alhaddadshop.com 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policies

**Privacy Policies**

Your privacy is of the highest importance to us, and we promise never to release your personal details to any outside company for mailing or marketing purposes. By visiting Al-Haddad Telecom portal, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

What Personal Information About Customers Does Al-Haddad Telecom Portal Gather?

 The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Al-Haddad Telecom Portal.

Information You Give Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.

Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies", and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Al-Haddad Telecom Portal.

E-mail Communications:

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Al-Haddad Telecom Portal if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences.

What about Cookies?

Cookies are electronic identifiers that are added to your computer's hard drive. This allows our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of products in your Shopping Cart between visits.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer.

However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Al-Haddad Telecom Portal essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add products to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Al-Haddad Telecom Portal products and services that require you to Sign in.

Does Al-Haddad Telecom Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not pass any details to other companies. We only share customer information with subsidiaries of Al-Haddad Telecom Portal.

Third-Party Service Providers:

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service.

They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

Protection of Al-Haddad Telecom Portal and Others:

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Al-Haddad Telecom Portal, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

How Secure Is My Credit Card Information

We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

Which Information Can I Access?

Al-Haddad Telecom gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Al-Haddad Telecom Portal for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

 What Choices Do I Have?

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Al-Haddad Telecom Portal features as your Profile and Customer Reviews.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in “My Account” When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Options settings which you can access from My Account. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of Al-Haddad Telecom Portal, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Al-Haddad Telecom Portal's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add products to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Al-Haddad Telecom Portal products and services that require you to Sign in.

Are Children Allowed to Use Al-Haddad Telecom Portal?

Al-Haddad Telecom Portal does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may browse the Al-Haddad Telecom Portal website but you cannot purchase any product without the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Al-Haddad Telecom Portal, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of Saudi Arabia. If you have any concern about privacy at Al-Haddad Telecom Portal, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
